One last thing before the night is over. I need people to stop telling me, well, why don't you go outside? That's not my role.
There's people who are outside who actually can't do what I do inside.
And there is a support that happens. That's that's what coalition building is between folks who are outside and inside and folks who do both.
There are artists and intellects and scholars who do not need to be in the outside of things.
We may not be the most effective there. We might be in the way there.
However, we support that work. We are buttressing that work.
We are bullhorning that work in ways that that work cannot be done.
And if in your mind it's, well, they're putting their lives in danger and you're not.
Trust me, they will come and knock on your door.
I hope this helps.
No way as hell.
Smart Bunny and!